import { Quiz } from '../../types';

const HairQuiz: Quiz[] = [
  {
    description: 'Jak to popisujeme?',
    name: 'Popis vlasy',
    questions: [
      {
        answer: ['raven hair'],
        question: 'havraní vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['black hair'],
        question: 'černé vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['blonde hair'],
        question: 'blonďaté vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['chestnut hair'],
        question: 'kaštanové vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['brown hair'],
        question: 'hnědé vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['dirty blonde hair'],
        question: 'špinavě blond vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['red hair'],
        question: 'zrzavé vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['ginger hair'],
        question: 'rezavé vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['grey hair'],
        question: 'šedé vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['bald'],
        question: 'pleš'
      },
      {
        answer: ['long hair'],
        question: 'dlouhé vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['short hair'],
        question: 'krátké vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['straight hair'],
        question: 'rovné vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['wavy hair'],
        question: 'vlnité vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['curly hair'],
        question: 'kudrnaté vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['fringe', 'bangs'],
        question: 'ofina'
      },
      {
        answer: ['thick hair'],
        question: 'husté vlasy'
      },
      {
        answer: ['thin hair'],
        question: 'řídké vlasy'
      }
    ]
  }
];

export default HairQuiz;
